superslots.com 2007-12-25

# Super Slots Privacy Policy - How to use this Online Slots Theme Casino Site

##  Privacy Policy 

EH New Ventures Inc. (EHNVI) is committed to respecting the privacy of all website visitors. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [superslots.com](http://www.superslots.com/)'s entire website.

EHNVI is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

**What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**

Visitors may receive - download - the casino software from the website. In order to do this, the visitor must enter their email address. When entered, the email is saved to a database along with the IP Address, date/time submitted and a unique visitor value as assigned by EHNVI.

**How it this information used?**

This information may be used as a communication tool to inquire about a visitor's download experience and/or to occasionally notify the visitor of important casino information as deemed necessary.

**Does the Super Slots website use cookies?**

Yes, the Super Slots site uses cookies. 

The cookies are only used to help determine from where the visitor originated. The cookie information is an anonymous profile of their origin as it relates to measuring our advertising.

Super Slots does not track a visitor's behavior on the website through use of cookies.

No personal information is stored regarding the visitor and the cookie is removed after 90 days from their original visit.

The cookie is only for the site the visitor is visiting. Super Slots does not look at any other cookies nor do we store information for other sites to use.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

EHNVI implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your information. User information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees with special access rights to such systems.

Your access to your Customer Status pages utilizes all appropriate security and encryptions methods provided by the VeriSign security system. This means that your information is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption.

This same technology is also employed when you place a casino chip/credit purchase request or access your information via our software. All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via 128- bit SSL technology.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can access your Customer Status pages on the website or login to the casino software without knowing your account number/user name and password. Do not share these with anyone.

**Does EHNVI disclose the information it collects from its website visitors to outside parties?**

No. EHNVI does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide while on the web site in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The company, in this case, would include a successor in title or a future owner of the business.

**How does a visitor opt-out, remove, or modify information they have provided to EHNVI through the website?**

EHNVI offers users the opportunity to unsubscribe so as not receive any future communications. This is achieved by one of three options:

  * Clicking on the unsubscribe link within the communication. Enter and submit the email address to be removed from our mailing list distribution.
  * Replying to a communication with the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.
  * Contacting the customer service support team by email.

**How are the website log files utilized?**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Third party links**

This site may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you're entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**Your consent**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by EHVNI. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Feedback**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this, or any other issue by email or by postal mail:

EH New Ventures Inc.  
P.O. Box W1143, Airport Rd.  
St. John's, Antigua  
West Indies

**Legal Disclaimer**

Please also visit our terms and conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the entire Super Slots web site and software.

Policy last updated, January 2002.
